Finding Aid to the Margaret Sanger papers SSC.MS.00138
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES I. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIAL, 1889-1995; undated
  - Personal records
    - Awards, honors, anniversaries, and degrees
      - Cordelia Scaife May, Chair of Family Planning at the University of West Virginia Medical School, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Margaret Sanger Award (to Lyndon Johnson), 1966 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Planned Parenthood, World Population Banquet, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Margaret Sanger exhibit and symposium, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Margaret Sanger College: Programs, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - National Women's Hall of Fame Award, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Arizona Hall of Fame, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - International Planned Parenthood Federation, New Delhi, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - American Humanist Association, Humanist of the Year, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Gold pendant (unidentified), undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Town Hall Club, 1935 (Box 12)
      - Family awards (milk carton tops), undated (Box 12)
      - Third Class Order of the Precious Crown (Japan), 1965 (Box 12)
      - Margaret Sanger Birth Control Conference, Zurich, 1930 (Box 12)
      - American Woman's Association, 1931 (Box 12)
    - Films and television
      - "No More Children" (early birth control film): Advertisement, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - "Birth Right" (script for documentary film), 1948 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Proposed film on life of Margaret Sanger, 1951-52 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Documentary by Herman Engel, 1965-66 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - "Freedom Forum,", 1952
        - General (Box 13, Folder 5)
        - Response against and for Margaret Sanger, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 6-9)
        - Mike Wallace interview, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 10)
        - Eisenhower and birth control, Tucson, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Homes
    - Willowlake
      - General, 1925-47 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Building and furnishings, 1922-23 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Tucson
      - General, 1942-43; 1956 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Sierra Vista, 1949-56 (Box 14, Folder 4-6)
      - Domestic help schedules, 1938; 1942 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Arizona activities
      - Arizona Children's Home Association, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Education, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - "Hoof Prints" (Arizona calendar of events), 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - University Methodist Church, 1950-54 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Tucson Festival of Arts, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Tucson Fine Arts Association, 1951; undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Tucson Medical Center
      - General, 1946; 1951 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Florence Rose, 1945-46 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Tucson Water Color Guild, 1950; 1951 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Miscellaneous Tucson events and organizations, 1939-61 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Margaret Sanger's death, 1966-67
      - Newspaper clippings (Box 16, Folder 1-14)
      - Memorial service, St. George's Episcopal Church (Box 16, Folder 15)
      - Congressional Record (Box 16, Folder 16)
      - Obituaries (Box 16, Folder 17)
      - List of obituary notices (Box 16, Folder 18)
      - Resolution relating to death of Margaret Sanger (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - Visitors to Margaret Sanger in nursing home in Tucson (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous memorabilia
      - Art exhibits, 1948-61 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Art work by Margaret Sanger, undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Bookplate designed by Rockwell Kent, 1939-49 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - "Bookworm" publication (related to Mary Higgins?), 1890 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Christmas cards (Sanger-Slee), 1945; undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Christmas gift lists, 1948; undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Christmas cards sent to Margaret Sanger, 1950-57 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Claverack College, 1889; 1939 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - Contributions, 1943-57 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - Corning, New York and Higgins family: Clippings and recent correspondence about, 1917-77 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - Drawing of M. Sanger/poem by Beatrice [?], signed by Sanger "To Leighton [Rollins], The Poet Jester" (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - Entertainment (guest lists, menus, etc.), 1946-53 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Fishkill, New York, undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
      - Genius analysis, 1932 (Box 17, Folder 14-15)
      - Hair (locks of Sanger's hair), undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
      - Herbs, undated (Box 17, Folder 17)
      - Immigrants (sponsorship of), 1938-41 (Box 17, Folder 18)
      - Interior decoration: New York School of Interior Design, undated (Box 17, Folder 19)
      - Invitations, 1932-62 (Box 18, Folder 1-3)
      - Japanese slippers (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Library of Congress, Sanger Collection
        - General, 1954; undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
        - Correspondence, 1965-66 (Box 18, Folder 6)
        - "A Catalogue of the Margaret Sanger Papers, 1914-1939, in the Library of Congress," prepared by Florence Rose, 1942 (Box 18, Folder 7-10)
      - Magazine subscriptions, 1942-53 (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Mailing lists, 1916-36 (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - Maine Chance Farm and Arizona Maine Chance, undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - Medical reports, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 14)
      - Membership cards, 1952-57 (Box 18, Folder 15)
      - Miscellaneous, 1936-58 (Box 18a, Folder 1)
      - Notes (miscellaneous), 1922-60 (Box 18a, Folder 2)
      - Overseas Associations Incorporated (food-gift parcel service), 1947; 1950 (Box 18a, Folder 3)
      - Persons associated with Sanger (lists), 1960; 1967 (Box 18a, Folder 4)
      - Psychic writing, undated (Box 18a, Folder 5)
      - Receipts, 1918-52 (Box 18a, Folder 6)
      - Social security card, undated (Box 18a, Folder 7)
      - Societas Rosicruciana in America, 1932-56 (Box 18a, Folder 8)
      - Suffrage posters (Box 18a, Folder 9)
        General
        [see Flat File, drawer 3]
      - Travel, 1929-59 (Box 18a, Folder 10)
      - War ration books, 1942-43 (Box 18a, Folder 11)
      - Additional artwork and memorabilia (Box 18a, Folder 12)
        [see SERIES X. OVERSIZE and flat file]
    - Research and publications about Sanger
      - Articles and biographical writings about Sanger, 1923-91 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Garrison, Webb, "Margaret Sanger: Rebel with a Cause", 1969 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Gaulard, Joan M., "Woman Rebel: A Rhetorical Analysis of Margaret Sanger and the Birth Control Movement in America, 1912-38," Ph.D. dissertation prospectus, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Gaulard, Joan M., "Woman Rebel: The Rhetorical Strategies of Margaret Sanger and the American Birth Control Movement 1912-1938", 1978 (Box 19)
      - Gaulard, Joan M., "Shall We Break This Law? A Critical Review of Margaret Sanger's Agitational Methods for the American Birth Control Movement," paper presented at the Indiana Speech Association, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Livingston, Barbara F., "Dreams and Inspirations: A Footnote to Biography of Margaret Sanger," thesis, Wesleyan University, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Hersey, Harold Brainerd, Margaret Sanger: The Biography of The Birth Control Pioneer, 1938 (Box 19, Folder 6)
        [See also SERIES VII. PRINTED MATERIAL-Books on shelf, for bound volume]
      - Ivins, Nancy Sanger and Margaret Sanger Marston, interview by Jacqueline Van Voris, transcription, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 7)
        [Audio recording located in SERIES VIII. Audiovisual materials]
      - Johnson, Malia Sedgewick, "Margaret Sanger and the Birth Control Movement in Japan, 1921-55," Ph.D. dissertation, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - Morehouse, William M., "The Speaking of Margaret Sanger in the Birth Control Movement from 1916 to 1937," Ph.D. dissertation, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Nicholson, Susan A., "Margaret Sanger, Rebellion and Respectability," thesis, Smith College, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Reed, James W., "Margaret Sanger," paper presented to the Berkshire Conference on the History of Women, October 25-26, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Richard, Olive Byrne, interview by Jacqueline Van Voris, November 25, 1977, transcription (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - Sands, Cohen and Donna M. Whalen, "William Sanger," research paper, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Sanger, Alexander Campbell, "Margaret Sanger: The Early Years, 1910-1917," undergraduate thesis, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Sanger, Grant, interview by Ellen Chesler, August 1976, transcription (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Sanger, Grant, interview by Jacqueline Van Voris, March 28, 1977, transcription (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - Simonds, Herbert, "Reminiscences of Herbert R. Simonds", undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Gray, Madeline, Margaret Sanger, typescript, undated (Box 21, Folder 2-6)
      - Biography by Lawrence Lader, 1955
        - Typescripts
          - copy 1 (Box 22, Folder 1-3)
          - copy 2 (Box 22)
        - Contract, publicity, reviews, lists, and miscellaneous clippings, 1952-57; undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
        - Notes (Box 23)
- SERIES II. WRITINGS AND SPEECHES, 1840-1980; undated
  Sanger's writings in the unfilmed portion of her papers contain a number of foreign language versions of Family Limitation; two editions of What Every Girl Should Know, an edition of What Every Mother Should Know; a large amount of correspondence related to distribution and complimentary copies of Sanger's 1938 Autobiography; notes on a proposed play about birth control (possibly written by Henriette Posner); and notes and research materials that were probably used for drafting articles and speeches. The writings series also contains material on Sanger's 1940 speaking tour of Massachusetts and the infamous Holyoke incident.
  - Pamphlets (non-US editions), 1916-33 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Debate on Birth Control (M. Sanger vs. Winter Russell), 1921 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - What Every Mother Should Know, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - What Every Girl Should Know, 1980 (reprint of 1920 ed.), undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Motherhood in Bondage: Transcriptions of letters and complimentary copy list, 1929-31 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Sayings of Others on Birth Control, New York Woman's Publishing Company, 1921 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - "Family Limitation": carbon copy, undated (Box 24, Folder 6a)
  - Autobiography
    - Correspondence, 1940-43 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Acknowledgments, 1941 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Governor's wives mailing, 1941 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Health and welfare groups, 1941-42 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Key contacts, 1941-42 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Mailing lists, 1941-42 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Medical Association replies, 1942 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Pioneer list, 1938 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Medical society presidents, 1941-42 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Norton publishers, 1940 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - State league lists and replies, 1941-43 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - "The Suppressed 'Obscene' Articles," [reprinted from The Woman Rebel, 1914], undated (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Magazine articles by Margaret Sanger, 1914-60 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Radio talks, 1935-53 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Speeches
    - Notes and research materials, 1940-1952 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Massachusetts lecture tour correspondence, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Untitled play about birth control: Notes by Henriette Posner, 1941 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Advertisements for Sanger writings, 1916; undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
- SERIES III. THIRD PARTY CORRESPONDENCE AND RELATED MATERIAL, 1877-1983
  Series III is arranged alphabetically by individual or organization and includes a correspondence file and/or other material (writings, clippings, reports) sorted in chronological order.
  This series includes correspondence regarding all aspects of the American and international birth control movements. The series incorporates correspondence, articles, reports and clippings related to Sanger's co-workers, other major players in the American birth control movement, particularly after 1930, and the chief organizers and financial supporters of the International Planned Parenthood Federation, established in 1952. This series also contains a significant amount of correspondence from Sanger family members and friends, and covers a wide range of projects and issues apart from birth control.
  Although most letters were filed under the author's name, each individual's file may contain both incoming and outgoing correspondence. Most letters written by secretaries or other organization staff were filed by recipient, as were letters written by little known or insignificant parties.
  Correspondence covering the major birth control organizations Sanger established, led, or in which she played a significant role is included in this series under individuals associated with a particular organization, as well as in SERIES IV. ORGANIZATIONS AND CONFERENCES, under the name of the organization. The series IV correspondence tends to relate specifically to the work of the organization: letters written and received on behalf of organization staff. Series III correspondence is more difficult to categorize. It typically covers much broader themes and is, generally, less relevant to a specific organization. The series III correspondence is also more personal and reflective of the work and concerns of the author/recipient. For a list of organization personnel for the sixteen organizations that Sanger was associated with, see the organizational histories in the guide to The Margaret Sanger Papers Microfilm Edition: Smith College Collection Series.
  The files of several individuals in series III include a significant amount of correspondence related to specific organizations. The Florence Rose file contains material on the BCCRB, the NCFLBC, the BCFA, and the PPFA. Robert Dickinson's correspondence concerns his advisory role with the BCCRB and the work of the National Committee on Maternal Health. The correspondence filed under Hannah Stone and Abraham Stone relates to the affairs of the BCCRB and MSRB, as well as various contraceptive research and writing projects. Information on the NCFLBC can be found under Hazel Moore, George Hastings and Margaret Valiant, among others. Correspondence concerning PPFA affairs is most concentrated in the files of William Vogt and D. Kenneth Rose, two national directors of the organization. Correspondence related to the IPPF and international work is more plentiful. Major participants in the international movement represented here include: Dorothy Brush, Clarence Gamble, Shidzue Kato, Dhanvanthi Rama Rau, Abraham Stone, Ellen Watumull, Edith How-Martyn, C. P. Blacker, and Vera Houghton. The file on Shidzue Kato contains significant documentation on the Japanese birth control movement. Correspondence under Charles Scribner, William Mathews, and Elizabeth Newman concerns General Douglas MacArthur's 1949 decision to deny Sanger a visa to enter Japan.
  Dorothy Brush's and Clarence Gamble's correspondence/biographical files, the two largest in the series, provide a wealth of information on particular aspects of the birth control movement. Brush, a close friend of Sanger, travelled with her on several trips to Europe and Asia, edited the IPPF newsletter, and provided funding for Sanger. Her correspondence offers a more intimate account of some of Sanger's activities and the emergence of an organized birth control movement in Asia. While the Sophia Smith Collection houses a separate collection of Brush's papers, some of her writings, including drafts of an article about her travels with Sanger, can be found here. Additional Brush correspondence is located in the Smith College Honorary Degree file in series I. Gamble was associated in one way or another with each organization Sanger led. His correspondence documents his multifaceted role as benefactor, medical researcher, and movement gadfly. His papers, including many publications and research reports, also describe the grass roots efforts to set up birth control clinics and organizations in Asia and many non-industrialized countries.
  Information on contraceptive research is scattered throughout the correspondence. In particular, the correspondence of Lydia DeVilbiss, Gamble, and Abraham and Hannah Stone offers important supplementary documentation to the Sanger correspondence in the microfilm edition. The DeVilbiss correspondence primarily concerns her controversial work on developing and testing a foam powder contraceptive designed to be used by the uneducated and the poor. Her correspondence with Abraham Stone is located in the Stone file.
  Reports, articles, and correspondence concerning the development of the anovulant pill can be found under Katharine Dexter McCormick, John Rock, and Gregory Pincus.
  This series contains approximately twenty client letters (filed under "client"): inquiries from men and women seeking contraceptive information. This is a small number compared to the several hundred that are included in the microfilm editions of the Smith College Collections and the Library of Congress collection of Sanger's papers, but it is a valuable resource since many thousands of these letters were treated as confidential medical records and most likely destroyed by Sanger and her co-workers.
  Printed material on the history of the English birth control movement and censorship is contained in the non-correspondence file of Annie Besant. Included are 19th century publications by Besant, information of the Besant-Bradlaugh trial, publications of the theosophical movement, and copies of Charles Knowlton's birth control tract, Fruits of Philosophy. Pamphlets and writings by Besant, C. R. Drysdale, Charles Vickery Drysdale, and Alice Drysdale Vickery also provide background on the Malthusian League, eugenics, and population control.
  Series III includes correspondence regarding efforts on the part of Sanger and Florence Rose, her long time secretary, to assist European refugees in emigrating to the U.S. during the late 1930s and 1940s. This correspondence is located under Anna Kreupl, Lilia Skala, Norbert Neufeld, Ludmilla Protitch, Leopold Pulitzer, Wilhelm Josefovitz, and Ludwig Chiavacci, and supplements the more extensive run of refugee correspondence in the microfilm edition.
  Significant correspondence between many of Sanger's closest friends can be found under Juliet Rublee, Dorothy Brush, Elizabeth Newman, Anne Kennedy, and Leighton Rollins, among others. The Rublee - Brush correspondence partially chronicles their long feud over who was most committed to Sanger's best interests. Much of the Rollins correspondence concerns his play about Sanger written in 1950. The Rollins, Brush, and Elizabeth Bacon correspondence also include discussions of Sanger's declining health during her final years.
  An exchange of love letters between Hugh de Selincourt and Francoise Cyon Lafitte is located in the Lafitte correspondence. The two carried on an affair for many years while Lafitte was living with Havelock Ellis and de Selincourt was married. Sanger's relevancy to this relationship (she was close friends and carried on long affairs with both de Selincourt and Ellis) is made apparent in her correspondence with Ellis, de Selincourt and Lafitte contained on both the Library of Congress and Smith College Collections microfilms.
  Series III contains important family correspondence and a few family records. The correspondence of Sanger's sisters, Anna Higgins, Ethel Byrne, and Mary Higgins includes several early letters. A large file concerning the disposition of William Purcell's (Sanger's maternal uncle) estate is located in the Anna Higgins correspondence. The non-correspondence file for Mary Higgins contains a journal (1895-1900) that includes passages on the death of their mother, Ann Purcell Higgins. The files on Sanger's sons, Grant and Stuart, are mostly composed of school and college records and early correspondence with friends and family. Included in Grant Sanger's correspondence are letters and cards written while escorting his mother on her ground-breaking 1922 world tour in which they travelled through Asia, northern Africa, and Europe. A few letters to Grant, Stuart and Peggy Sanger from their father are found under William Sanger, along with an early and barely legible diary. The large file on J. Noah Slee contains correspondence concerning the Three-in-One Oil Company, loans and investments; correspondence with business associate Norman Bray; and correspondence with his sons and daughter. Some of Slee's correspondence as treasurer of the BCCRB and NCFLBC is located in the correspondence files of the organizations in series IV. The non-correspondence filed under Slee includes divorce papers from his first marriage; expense books dating from 1891, address books, passports and appointment books; and horoscopes and psychic writings.
  - Alden, Sue, 1938; 1962 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Ames, Blanche, undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Ashley, Grace H., 1937; 1938 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - A, 1929-52 (Box 26, Folder 4-5)
  - Bacon, Elizabeth Grew, 1942-62 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Barnes, Harry Elmer, 1952; undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Benjamin, Hazel C., 1932-34 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Besant, Annie, 1878-1933 (Box 26, Folder 9-11)
  - Bingham, Mary C., 1944-46 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Black, Algernon D., 1934; 1935; undated (Box 26, Folder 13-14)
  - Blacker, C.P., 1951-59 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Blossom, Frederick, 1918-22 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Brandt, Zelma, 1939; 1941 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Brock, Marion Willis, 1935-42 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Brush, Dorothy Hamilton, 1931-66 (Box 27, Folder 1-4)
  - Buck, Pearl, 1934-44 (Box 27, Folder 5-6)
  - Buckman, Rilma S., 1937-47 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Burch, Guy Irving, 1932-45 (Box 27, Folder 8-9)
  - Byrne, Ethel Higgins, 1918(?); undated (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - B, 1926-60 (Box 27, Folder 11-12)
  - Cadbury, George, 1958; 1959 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Cass, Muriel, 1936-38 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Chiavacci, Ludwig, 1939-41 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Client letters, 1935-51 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Clyde, Ethel, 1939-50 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Cook, Adelaide Pearson, 1918-66 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Cook, Robert C., 1953; 1955 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Cox, Charles, 1937; 1945 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Cox, Harold, 1945; undated (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - C, 1911-57 (Box 27, Folder 22-23)
  - Day, Jr., Rufus S., 1956-70 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Delp, Mildred, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Dennett, Mary Ware, 1918; 1928 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - DeSelincourt, Hugh, 1921-28 (Box 28, Folder 1-4a)
  - DeVilbiss, Lydia Allen, 1935-52 (Box 28, Folder 5-6)
  - Dickinson, Robert L., 1929-43 (Box 28, Folder 7-8)
  - DiGregorio, John, 1943; undated (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Drysdale, C.R., 1877-1904 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Drysdale, Charles Vickery, 1877-1923 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - D, 1938-58 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - East and West Foundation, 1935-44 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Ellis, Havelock, 1898-1939 (Box 29, Folder 5-6)
  - Ernst, Morris Leopold, 1936; 1966 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - E, 1948 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Faggi, John and Beatrice, 1935; 1946 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Fehring, Albert M., 1947 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Ferguson, Rev. George, 1940 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Fuld, Carrie B.F., 1942 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Furst, F. Sidonie Chiavacci, undated (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - F, 1936-60 (Box 29, Folder 14-15)
  - Gamble, Sarah, 1953; 1955 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Gamble, Clarence (includes letters to Shidzue Kato, Arnold Toynbee, Dharivanthi Rama Rau, Dorothy Brush, Elise Ottesen-Jensen), 1937-70 (Box 29, Folder 17-18)
  - Gates, Edith, 1954-59 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Gilman, Mildred, 1953 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Goetting, Betty Mary, 1949; 1950 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Goldstein, Jonah J., 1966 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Gordon, Leon, 1941 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Greenbaum, Wolff, and Ernst, 1933-41 (Box 30, Folder 4)